Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Printed Ephemera Collection on Students for a Democratic Society PE.035
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: Radical Education Project Publications, 1963-1970; 1.75 Linear Feet in 1 record carton, 1 shared manuscript box, and 1 shared oversize box
  - Literature Lists, 1967-1969 (Box 5)
  - Newsletter, 1967-1969 (Box 5)
  - Pamphlets and Publications, 1966-1970, undated (Box 5)
  - Pamphlets and Publications: Black America/Racism, 1967, undated (Box 5, Box Shared Tamiment 189, Folder 13)
  - Pamphlets and Publications: Book Critiques, undated (Box 5)
  - Pamphlets and Publications: China, undated (Box 5)
  - Pamphlets and Publications: Draft Resistance, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Box Shared Tamiment 189, Folder 12)
  - Pamphlets and Publications: Education, 1967-1968, undated (Box 5)
  - Pamphlets and Publications: Imperialism/Third World, 1964-1968, undated (Box 5)
  - Pamphlets and Publications: Labor I, circa 1960-1970, undated (Box 5)
  - Pamphlets and Publications: Labor II, 1960-1970 (Box 5)
  - Pamphlets and Publications: Latin America, 1963-1967, undated (Box 5)
  - Pamphlets and Publications: Middle East, circa 1967 (Box 5)
  - Pamphlets and Publications: Mother Jones, circa 1970 (Box 5)
  - Pamphlets and Publications: Political Economy I, 1963-1967, undated (Box 5)
  - Pamphlets and Publications: Political Economy II, 1963-1967, undated (Box 5)
  - Pamphlets and Publications: Power Structure, undated (Box 5)
  - Pamphlets and Publications: Radicalism/New Left, 1965-1968, undated (Box 5)
  - Pamphlets and Publications: Women's Liberation, 1966-1970, undated (Box 5)
  - "Radicals in the Professions" Conference, 1967 (Box 5)
  - Reports and Proposals, 1967-1969, undated (Box 5)
  - Broadside: Chicago - October 11, 1979 (Box Shared Tamiment 007, Folder 4)